stephenbigalow.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy

By using or accessing CandlestickForum content or a CandlestickForum web site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term “CandlestickForum ” (also “we ” or “us “) includes CandlestickForum, LLC and its related companies, subsidiaries, and brands, including without limitation all web sites operated by these entities. Such web sites include, without limitation, CandlestickForum.com, CandlestickForum/members.com, CandlestickForum/partners.com, StephenBigalow.com, HistoryOfTheNorthPole.com, StephenBigalowPartners.com,  and sub-domains thereto.

**What information does CandlestickForum.com gather?**  
There are two types of personally identifiable information CandlestickForum may obtain from you: (1) information you may choose to submit to us, and (2) information we collect as you interact with a CandlestickForum web site or if you respond to one of our materials available through CandlestickForum and/or Stephen Bigalow social media sites.Together, this is “User Information. ”

User Information submitted to CandlestickForum includes all information you may submit for purposes of registering to receive CandlestickForum subscriptions or services, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, or payment information, as well as in some cases selection of a username and password. You may also submit online comments or responses to surveys that we send you.

User Information about online browsing or access includes such things as “cookies, ” which are pieces of data stored on a user’s computer tied to information about that user, to make online browsing more efficient. We also collect information on how users access and browse CandlestickForum web sites. This information may or may not be identifiable, and it may include statistics about the numbers and timing of unique visits to our web site(s), repeat visits, and which pages are viewed. Information we collect may also include email delivery behavior, such as if you received an email we sent you, if you opened it, how many times you opened the email, if you clicked on a URL in the email, which URL you clicked on, and how many times you clicked on a URL.

**How does CandlestickForum use personal information?**  
CandlestickForum uses User Information to provide services and products that you request, and to analyze trends, administer the site and email delivery, track user movement, and gather aggregate information.

In addition, by subscribing to a free or paid newsletter or other CandlestickForum service, you agree to receive and may receive marketing emails from CandlestickForum relating to its other newsletters or services, potentially including trial or free subscriptions. We may also use your IP address to present you with more customized offers for services, such as those specific to certain geographic regions of the country or of the world. Pursuant to the federal CAN-SPAM Act, you may opt out of receiving marketing messages from CandlestickForum through an “opt-out ” link at the bottom of any CandlestickForum promotional email.

User Information about online browsing or access includes such things as “cookies, ” which are pieces of data stored on a user’s computer tied to information about that user, to make online browsing more efficient. We also collect information on how users access and browse CandlestickForum web sites. This information may or may not be identifiable, and it may include statistics about the numbers and timing of unique visits to our web site(s), repeat visits, and which pages are viewed. Information we collect may also include email delivery behavior, such as if you received an email we sent you, if you opened it, how many times you opened the email, if you clicked on a URL in the email, which URL you clicked on, and how many times you clicked on a URL.

CandlestickForum may also send CAN-SPAM Act compliant email advertisements or messages on behalf of third-party advertisers to anyone who signs up, registers or subscribes to any of our services. We do not sell or transfer your email address to these third parties unless you specifically request information from one of our co-registration advertisers by selecting or leaving selected the check box next to the co-registration offer. Pursuant to the CAN-SPAM Act, you may opt-out from receiving third-party promotional messages at any time through an “opt-out ” link at the bottom of any CandlestickForum promotional email.

**How do we share information?**  
CandlestickForum may share User Information with our vendors or contractors who provide certain services for us, such as subscription fulfillment, delivery of email, and management of online surveys. This information is shared with these CandlestickForum vendors or contractors only for the purpose of providing these services or functions. In addition, to the extent that you submit comments or survey responses, you understand and agree we may use those responses, including by posting them online with your name or username, as applicable.

We may provide our advertisers with non-identifiable email behavior information on an aggregated basis such as email delivery information, email open rate information, and URL click tracking information.

If CandlestickForum is ever sold, acquired, or merged, in whole or part (including a sale of one or more discrete publications, brands, or departments), any User Information may be transferred to one or more separate successor entity or entities. CandlestickForum subscribers and registered users will be notified of such a change in ownership, merger or acquisition.

**Co-registration, third party advertisements, and links**  
CandlestickForum may display on its web sites advertisements from third party advertisers who are interested in reaching our audience. We only transmit your information to a third-party advertiser if you elect to receive a special offer from that advertiser through our co-registration service (either by selecting or by leaving selected the check box next to the advertiser’s offer). The information we transmit in this instance may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address, phone number, IP address and the date you registered for the third party offer. We may also transmit information about our visitors and subscribers collected through the registration process as well as through any online surveys we may conduct.

Although CandlestickForum attempts to accept advertisements from responsible third party advertisers, we make no representations or guarantees about such third parties. You understand that if you choose to register with or enter into a transaction with any third-party advertiser based on an advertisement or offer found on a CandlestickForum web site, within a CandlestickForum email, or via any other delivery method (including, but not limited to, postal mail),that such a third party advertiser is separate from CandlestickForum and that CandlestickForum is not responsible or liable for any action or omission by the third-party advertiser.

Similarly, CandlestickForum web sites may contain links to other web sites. We cannot be and are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave a CandlestickForum web site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by CandlestickForum.

**Changes to this policy**  
Your use of CandlestickForum web site(s), and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms and Conditions of Service ( “TCS “) and all of its dispute resolution provisions. We may modify this Privacy Policy effective immediately upon notice to you either by (1) electronic mail or conventional mail or (2) posting to a CandlestickForum web site (which shall be deemed constructive notice). Your continued use of any CandlestickForum web site following notice of any modification to this Privacy Policy shall be conclusively deemed an acceptance of all such modification(s). We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Where to Direct Questions About CandlestickForum, LLC’s Privacy Policy**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us here:

CandlestickForum, LLC  
39 W Trace Creek Dr  
The Woodlands, TX 77381  
1-866-251-4015
